Higher Power is a science fiction, action, thriller
film directed by Matthew Charles Santoro.
When the Universe decides what it wants, it's pointless to resist.
With his family's life at stake, Joseph Steadman finds himself the unwilling test subject of
a maniacal scientist in a battle that could save the world – or destroy it.
Joe Steadman, played by Ron Eldard.
Zoe Steadman, played by Jordan Danger.
Michael, played by Austin Stowell.
Control, played by Colm Feore.
Heather Steadman, played by Jade Tailor.
Tele, played by Winston James Francis.
Higher Power is a 2018 science fiction action thriller
film directed by Matthew Charles Santoro.
It is about an ordinary man faced with the task of
saving the world from destruction.
It was released on May 11, 2018.
It stars Jordan Hinson, Ron Eldard, Colm Feore, Austin
Stowell,  Jade Tailor and Tom Wright.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.